Guide to the Boy Scouts of America Collection of ephemeral material, 1838-1993
Department of Special Collections
- Series III: Pamphlets, Guides, and Handbooks
  - Animal Tracks - and how to know them (Reprint from Virginia Wildlife Magazine of December 1953) n.d. (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Back Packing Principles (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - A Balanced Annual Council Program of Activities n.d. (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Booth Show Midway n.d. (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - A boy, a man, a program, an idea, an ideal, and action n.d. (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Boy Scouts and Cooperation n.d. (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Boy Scouts of America - A Program With a Purpose n.d. (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Boy Scouts of America Scouting Accident Insurance (No. 10-101) n.d. (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Boy Scouts of America Service Library n.d. (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Buddy Check Board for Camp Waterfront n.d. (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Camp Cooking n.d. (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Campfires n.d. (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Camping n.d. (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Camping Standards n.d. (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Camping the Camporee Way n.d. (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - The Campmaster Corps n.d. (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Camp Nature Lore n.d. (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Campsite Instructions n.d. (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Communications n.d. (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Congratulations Mr. Scoutmaster n.d. (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Cooking Reservation n.d. (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Court of Honor Requirements n.d. (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Courts of Honor n.d. (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Czternascie Powodow Dlaczego (Polish) n.d. (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Den Leader Reminder n.d. (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Disease Carrier - The Fly n.d. (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Drill Regulations, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - The Elks and the Boy Scouts n.d. (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Emergerncy Foods n.d. (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Excitement on Wheels n.d. (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Exploring a Professional Career in Scouting n.d. (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - February-Exploring Pledge Month n.d. (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - 50 Outstanding Books for Boy Scouts and Also 25 Good Books for Cubs Published During 1938 n.d. (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - "Fit For Tomorrow": A Physical Fitness Guide and Personal Record n.d. (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Food Cost Accounting and Cooking Gear Helps n.d. (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Forward on Liberty's Team Troop Annual Report n.d. (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Forward on Liberty's Team - The Three Year Program n.d. (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Fourteen Reasons Why n.d. (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Great Athletes Keep Fit n.d. (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Ground-to-Aid Distress Code n.d. (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Growing Men To Strengthen America n.d. (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Guide to Selecting n.d. (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Health and Safety n.d. (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Hiking Goals n.d. (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - A Housing Project Janitor Turns Teen Gangs into Boy Scout Troops (Reprint from Chicago Daily News 2/8/64) n.d. (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - How Boy's Life Helps the Scoutmaster n.d. (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - How To Secure A Scoutmaster: Six Sure Steps n.d. (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - The How's of Hiking n.d. (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - How to Use and Lead Games n.d. (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Ice Accident Prevention and Rescue n.d. (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Ideal Troop Site Layout n.d. (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Invest in Boyhood in the Red River Valley Council n.d. (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - An Invitation to Consider a Career in Scouting n.d. (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - An Invitation "... to secure the blessings of liberty to ourselves and our posterity " n.d. (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Knots and How To Tie Them n.d. (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - The Legion Extends a Hand - To Boys n.d. (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Let's Go Camping n.d. (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Let's Take a Hike n.d. (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - The Lone Scout Plan n.d. (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Massawepie Outpost Camps Trail Guide n.d. (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Mimetic Exercises for Boys n.d. (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Minimum Standards for Boy Scout Camps n.d. (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Mitigua Songs n.d. (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - More Good Scouts n.d. (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Mountain Climbing for the Scout Show n.d. (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Needed: More Scout Units n.d. (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - On My Honor n.d. (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Onward for God and My Country n.d. (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Onward for God and My Country: The Four Year Program n.d. (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Order of the Arrow-Ordeal Honor Booklet n.d. (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Our Best Hope For Peace n.d. (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Our Boys and Scouting (No. 4803) n.d. (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Our Heartiest Congratulations on Your Becoming a Scout n.d. (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Out With It! n.d. (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Outdoor Programs n.d. (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Patrol Work Bench n.d. (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Physical Development n.d. (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Pioneering n.d. (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Presenting the Years Between n.d. (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - A Preview of a Professional Career in Scouting n.d. (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Principles and Organization of the Scouting Show n.d. (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - A Recruiting Plan n.d. (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Red River Valley Council Policy of Organization and Promotion of "Cubbing" n.d. (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Revised Outline of Experimental Air Scout Leader's Training Course n.d. (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Rules of Standard Contest Events - Bronx Valley n.d. (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Rural Boys Want Scouting n.d. (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Safe Swim Defense n.d. (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - For Troops
  - For Troops and Posts
  - Scout Council Paper Recycling Kit n.d. (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Scout Program Quiz Book n.d. (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Scouters' Course in Health and Safety n.d. (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Scouting and Organized Athletics n.d. (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Scouting Around the World n.d. (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Scouting As Evangelism n.d. (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Scouting for Boys n.d. (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Scouting Ideals n.d. (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Scouting Today's a Lot More Than You Think n.d. (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Scouts Are Campers (Reprint From Boy's Life 6/39) n.d. (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Send Him To Camp Because n.d. (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Senior Scout Ceremonies n.d. (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Sing Scout Sing: Songs for Camp n.d. (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Skeleton Constitution n.d. (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Skill-O-Rama n.d. (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Slums Cost You Too Much Money, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Star Casting n.d. (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Suggested Boy Scout Activities for Booth Shows n.d. (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - They Say... Scouting is OK n.d. (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - This is Scouting in the Upper Mohawk Council n.d. (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - A Tribute to the Boy Scouts of America n.d. (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Troop Fireguard Plan and Chart (No. 3695) n.d. (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - The Troop Review Board n.d. (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Troop Stunts n.d. (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Try A Boy Scout Project-O-Ree! n.d. (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - The Twelfth Scout Law n.d. (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Using Experience Problems To Teach First Aid n.d. (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - A Way of Assured Advancement in Your Troop n.d. (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Ways for Units to Earn Money n.d. (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - We the People: Building a Strong America n.d. (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Webelos-Dad Outing n.d. (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - "Welcome Scouters!" Ceremony n.d. (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - What Cubbing Is n.d. (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - What is a Boy Scout? n.d. (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - What is Scouting? n.d (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - What Scouting Will Mean to You n.d.. (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Where Does Your Boy's Time Go? n.d. (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Whirling Wheels - A Specialty Act Fot The Scout Show n.d. (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - The Whole Scout Family n.d. (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Wood Badge Course n.d. (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Woodcarving n.d. (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Woodcraft n.d. (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - World Friendship Fund n.d. (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Young, Whitney M. Jr. Executive Director, National Urban League n.d. (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Your Camp is Not Fire Proof n.d. (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Your Job in a Nut Shell - The Troop Committee n.d. (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Series IV: Awards, Insignias, Merit Badges, and Uniforms
  - Merit Badge Examiners (ca. 1930) (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - The President Franklin D. Roosevelt 1933 Ten Year Program Award 9/20/33 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - District #4 - Hendrick Hudson Council Court of Awards Program Schedule n.d. (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - The Twentieth Anniversary of Troop S-105. Atlantic District 11/30/36 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Official patches from all six National Boy Scout Jamborees 1937-1964 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Official Program: Boy Scout Exposition. Yonkers Armory 2/12/38 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Camden County Boy Scouts Merit Badge Show. New Jersey 4/29-30/38 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Supplement to Handbook for Boys. Changes in Requirements, Badges and Insignia 7/1/41 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Merit Badge Counselor Guide 1943 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Region Four - Ohio. Silver Antelope Awards 10/25/47 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - For Good Appearance... Have Every Scout in Your Unit "look like a Scout" (ca. 1947) (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Merit Badge Application (ca. 1948) (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Arrowhead Honor Award. (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Mount Rainier Council 10/52
    - Central NC Council 5/7/54>
    - Tall Corn Area Council 11/16/55
  - Application for Award of Eagle Rank (No. 6109 n.d./Cat. No. 6109A ca. 1952) (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Letter to Curt Weber from S. Tebo, BSA Jamboree patch 8/13/64 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Scouter Recognition For Training and Service 1967 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Hike and Trails Award Program. Los Angeles Area Council, CA (ca. 1968) (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Region Six - Georgia. Silver Antelope Awards 10/24/69 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Application For Merit Badge (No. 4124) (ca.1969) (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Region 6 Boypower Banquet 1969 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - National President's Unit Award 1976 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Scout Unit Award and Nomination Form. Freedoms Foundation at Valley Forge (ca. 1976) (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Cub Scout and Webelos Scout Uniform Inspection Sheet 1985 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Merit Badge Counselor Orientation 1987 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Adventure... That's Scouting! It Always Starts With His Uniform n.d. (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Application For Life Saving Award n.d. (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Application For Merit Badge (No. 4409) n.d. (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Application For Training Award n.d. (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Boy Scout Uniforms From All The World and How to Make Them n.d. (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Citations. Silver Buffalo Award n.d. (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Commissioner's Arrowhead Honor Award n.d. (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Court of Honor Examinations and Awards. Schedule and Rules n.d. (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Cub Scout Uniform Inspection Sheet n.d. (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Directions for Making a Turk's Head Neckerchief Slide n.d. (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Firemanship Merit Badge Requirements n.d. (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - First Class Scoreboard n.d. (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Give Him a Chance (Merit Badge Plan) n.d. (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - The Honor Unit Award n.d. (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - How to Stage a Successful Uniform Inspection n.d. (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - How to Wear Your Leggings n.d. (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Inspection Report of Uniform and Appearance n.d. (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - All Scouters
    - Boy Scouts (Forms ADV-006 350M863, 500M 8-65, & 500M961)
    - Boy Scouts and Explorers in Troops
    - Boy Scouts at Summer Camp
    - Cub Scouts
    - Pack and Troop Scouters (Forms ADV-008 50M863, 75M262, 100M 10-65, & 60-008 20M960)
  - Lady Scouters Uniform Inspection Sheet n.d. (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Leadership Corps Uniform Inspection Sheet, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Letter to Scouters on BSA custom design emblem service n.d. (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Merit Badge Application (Form 66) n.d. (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Merit Badge Application (Form 251) n.d. (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Merit Badge Application. Lower Anthracite District n.d. (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Merit Badge Counselor Information n.d. (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Merit Badge Counselor Registration Cards n.d. (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - National Camping Award n.d. (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Official Uniforms For Scouts n.d. (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Otetiana Council BSA badge receipt n.d. (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Pedro Award n.d. (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Revised Requirements n.d. (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Scout Shop Uniform Mail Order Forms. Toronto, Ontario n.d. (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - The Scout Uniform: How It Helps To Make a Better Scout n.d. (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Scout Uniform Inspections n.d. (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Scout Uniform Inspection Sheet n.d. (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Scouter Uniform Inspection Sheet n.d. (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Scouter's Wife Award n.d. (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Trail's End Gourmet PopcornOutstanding Salesmanship Award n.d. (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Training Recognition Plan n.d. (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Troop Roll Call and Uniform Inspection n.d. (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Uniform Inspection Unit Award n.d. (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Webelos Scout Uniform Inspection Sheet n.d. (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Wood Badge Beads n.d. (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Your Opportunity As A Merit Badge Counselor n.d. (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Series V: Certificates, Charters, and Commissions
  - Patrol Leader's Certificate of Training. Troop 37, Tulsa Area 4/15/45 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Junior Leader's Training Conference Certificate. Post 36, Central NC Council 9/17-18/54 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Junior Leader's Training Course Certificate. Troop Post 70, Yohogania Area Council 4/24-26/59 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Certificate of Outstanding Contribution to Youth. Tall Corn Area Council 4/13/55 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Boy Scout Service Training Certificate. Camp Kilworth, Tacoma, WA 2/3/52 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Certificate of Commissioner Training. Schiff Scout Reservation 1/11/59 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Warrants (pre and post- ca. 1959) (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Assistant Senior Patrol Leader
  - Den Chief
  - Junior Assistant Scoutmaster
  - Instructor
  - Patrol Leader
  - Senior Patrol Leader
  - Warrant Officer
  - Scouting Skills Activity Trail Certificate of Completion. Silver Springs Encampment 10/19/63 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - National Council Certificate of Appreciation for the Commemorative Tribute. Washington, D.C. 11/7/64 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Follow the Rugged Road to Adventure Certificate of Appreciation (ca. 1965) (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Troop Charter. (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Exchange Club. Troop 566, Sharpesburg, NC 11/31/66 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Memorial Methodist Church. Troop 121, Thomasville, NC 1/31/67 & 1/31/69 -72 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Twin Parent Teacher Organization. Troop 29, Bourneville, OH 12/31/71 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Commissioner's Conference - How to Train District Commissioners (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Certificate of Webelos Scout Graduation. Pack 27, Rockford, IL 6/27/68 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Certificate of Training Recognition Plan - Scouter's Key 11/8/74 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Explorer Charters. (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Schiff Scout Reservation. Post 604, Mendham, NJ 11/30/72 &74 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Gary Memorial United Methodist. Post 9057, Daniels, MD 4/30/75 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Bicentennial Declaration Certificates 1976. (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Council Appreciation
    - Council Awareness
    - Chartered Organization
  - National President's Leader of Distinction Certificate 1976 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Explorer Certificate of Appreciation for Post 604 President 1977-1978 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - A Commisioner's Pledge 1/28/78 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - National Eagle Scout Association Certificate of Appreciation for Youth Advisor 2/5/78 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Cub Scout Program Certificate of Appreciation. Pack 934 5/30/78 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Call to Liberty Scouting Plan Certificate n.d. (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Certificate of Den Chief Appointment n.d. (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Certificate of Webelos Scout Rank and Tenderfoot Scout Eligibility. Pack 2, Tulsa Area n.d. (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Cub Scout Pack Graduation Certificate n.d. (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - District Appreciation Certificate n.d. (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - "Family Alert" Pack Citation n.d. (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Forward On Liberty's Team Members' Pledge n.d. (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Junior Leader's Certificate of Training n.d. (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Librarian's Certificate n.d. (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Local Standard Rating Certificate n.d. (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - National Camping Award Certificate n.d. (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - National Council Scout Movement in the Training of Other Leaders Certificate n.d. (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Pack Appreciation Certificate n.d. (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Patrol Leader's Certificate n.d. (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - "Prepared" Troop Citation n.d. (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Purdy Pact Good Turn-Nature Conservation-Training Certificate. Washington Irving Council n.d. (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - "Ready" Explorer Unit Citation n.d. (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Scoutmaster's Right Way Citation n.d. (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - 75th Diamond Jubilee Certificate of Appreciation n.d. (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Sustaining Membership Enrollment Certificate of Appreciation. Atalanta Area Council n.d. (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Three Year Training Program Certificate n.d. (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Training Recognition Plan Certificate n.d. (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Unit Leader Commision n.d. (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Series VI: Banquets, Dances, and Dinners
  - The Annual Gathering in Good Fellowship of Scouters and their Ladies of the Erie County Council. Buffalo, NY 11/11/32 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Annual Minstrel and Dance, Troop 24. Providence, Rhode Island 2/22/33 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Dinner & Reception to the Scoutmasters and their Wives. Second District: Fenimore Cooper Council. White Plains N.Y. 11/26/34 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - 8th Annual Boy Scout Dinner. Tamaqua District 2/14/35 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Annual Southeast Banquet 1/21/36 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - 12th Annual Banquet, Troop 6. North Tarrytown, NY 2/12/36 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - 42nd Anniversary Dinner. Cincinnati Area Council. 2/23/56 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Region Six - Georgia. (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Annual Banquet 4/5/57
    - Annual Banquet 3/21/61
  - Golden Jubilee Annual Fellowship Dinner. Elizabeth, NJ 3/19/60 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Annual Fellowship Dinner. Union Council. Elizabeth, NJ 3/25/61 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Court of Honor and Dinner. Linwood, NJ 1/12/62 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - 50th Anniversary Banquet and Reunion. Troop 6, Brookline, MA 4/23/66 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Annual Scouter's Appreciation Dinner. Crawford District: Washington Trail Council. Vernon, NY 4/4/63,4/14/66, & 4/13/67 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Joe A. Clement Retirement Dinner 11/21/66 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Series VII: Boy Scout Night/Week
  - First Annual Boy Scout Night. Hastings-on-Hudson Scouting Organization 2/14/36 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Boy Scout Week 1950 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Boy Scout Week Program Kit 1952 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Boy Scout Week Program Kit 1953 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Boy Scout Week. Washington, D.C. 2/7-13/60 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Boy Scout Week Parent's Night 1963 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Scout Week. 2/7-13/63 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Boy Scout Week Kit 2/7-13/66 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Tarhe Scouting District. Window Displays, Scout Week 1989 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Invitation to Boy Scout Week and the New Four-Year Program, Rhode Island n.d. (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Series VIII: Camporees/Jamborees and Gather-ees
  - National Jamboree letterhead. Washington, D.C. 1937 4, 6 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    Cavalcade of Scouting Camporee Arena Show. Waters Stadium, N.J. 8/3/38
  - Program for Annual Gather-ee and Court of Awards. Dobbs Ferry, NY 6/23-24/39 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - National Jamboree. Irvine Ranch, CA 1953 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - National Scout Jamboree. Colorado Springs, CO 1960 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - White Oak District Camporee Morning Worship Program 8/26/62 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Sixth National Jamboree. Valley Forge, PA 7/19/64 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - World Jamboree "For Friendship" Stamps. Idaho 1967 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - National Scout Jamboree "Camp Waite Phillips" card and mailing envelopes. Farragut State Park, Idaho 7/16-22/69 (Box 4, Folder 9&10)
  - National Scout Jamboree. Morraine Park, PA 1973 (Box 5, Folder 1&2)
  - Telegrams to parents from Scout and Leader on trip to World Exposition in Paris 1937 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Fall Friendship Camporee, Camp Shaginappi. District Nine 10/11-13/74 (Box 5, Folder 4&5)
  - National Scout Jamboree. Moraine State Park, PA 8/3-9/77 (Box 5, Folder 4&5)
  - DalaJamb. Kopparbo, Sweden 7/14-24/79 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - National Scout Jamboree. A.P. Hill, VA 7/29-8/4/81 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Pickens District Camporee 11/5-7/1982 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - National Scout Jamboree. A.P. Hill, Virginia 7/24-30/85 (Box 5, Folder 8&9)
  - National Scout Jamboree. Fort A.P. Hill, Virginia 8/2-8/89 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - National Scout Jamboree 1993 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Diamond Jubilee Jamboree Tickets n.d. (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Fourth National Jamboree Historic Valley Forge tour guide and map n.d. (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Jamboree Camp Administration Instructions n.d. (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Sixth Nationl Jamboree Shooting Activity registration and scoring card n.d. (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Series IX: Camp-o-ramas and Scout-o-ramas
  - The Boy Scout-O-Rama. Madison Square Garden, NY 1940 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Scout-O-Rama. New York State Armory, Elmira, NY 4/15/44 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Scout-O-Rama. Elmira, NY 6/14/47 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - 6th Annual Scout-O-Rama. San Fernando Valley Council, CA 1948 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Scout-O-Rama Program Content. Greater New York Councils 1/21/48 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Scout-O-Rama Preview. Madison Square Gardens, NY 5/22/48 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - North Bergen Camp-O-Rama. Teaneck, New Jersey 1951 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Buffalo Area Council Scout-O-Rama 5/25-26/51 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Scout-O-Rama. Cornell University, NY 3/25/61 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Scout-O-Rama. Morristown Armory, NJ 5/19-20/61 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Scout-O-Rama. Finger Lakes Council. Geneva, NY 5/20/61 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Blue Water Council Golden Anniversary Scout-O-Rama. Port Huron, MI 5/16-17/70 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Wonderful World of Scouting Scout-O-Rama. Port Huron, MI 5/13-14/72 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Series X: Conferences and Meetings
  - 15th Annual Regional (Region 10) Convention. Nicollet Hotel, Minneapolis, MN 11/2/34 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Letter announcing the Annual Business Meeting of the Detroit Lakes District Scout Committee 1/2/35 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - 25th Anniverary Celebration of the Boy Scouts 6/29/35 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Annual Convention. Region 10. Aberdeen, SD 10/30-31 and Dultuh, MN 11/1/35 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - 14th International Scout Conference. Valduz, Liechtenstein 8/8-13/37 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Half Moon Training Troop Meeting, Scarborough, New York 5/20/38 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Invitation to Attend the Annual Meeting of the Hendrick Hudson Council. North Tarrytown, NY 1/21/39 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Twentieth Annual Meeting and Scoutmaster's Appreciation Banquet. Shreveport, LA 1/25/40 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Region Six - Georgia. Annual Meeting 3/21/41 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Thirty-First Annual Meeting, Central Ohio Area Council. Columbus, Ohio 1/28/42 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Annual Meeting, Harding Area Council. Marion, Ohio 1/19/44 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - The Thirty-Fourth Annual Meeting of the Chicago Council - BSA 1/10/45 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Organization Meeting. Lewis-Clark Council, Lewis-Clark Hotel, ID 9/14/45 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - 42nd Annual Meeting. National Council. NY 5/23/52 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Family Vacation Plus Training, Volunteer Training Center, Philmont, NM 1955 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Explorer Leaders
    - Boy Scout Leaders
    - Finance Training Conference
    - District Chairmen Conferences
  - Conferences, Philmont, NM 1956 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Explorers Leaders